{
    "Smashing English (50 idioms)": [
        {"front": "Running on empty", "back": "living without energy"},
        {"front": "Pull yourself together", "back": "calm down"},
        {"front": "a bone to pick with someone", "back": "annoyed by other with light reason"},
        {"front": "on thin ice", "back": "close to be in trouble"},
        {"front": "all doom and gloom", "back": "only see bad things in life"},
        {"front": "snowed under", "back": "someone has so much work"},
        {"front": "work every hour the god sends", "back": ""},
        {"front": "live hand to mouth", "back": ""},
        {"front": "couldn't care less", "back": ""},
        {"front": "daylight robbery", "back": ""},
        {"front": "don't hold your breath", "back": "don't expect something"},
        {"front": "a shoulder to cry on", "back": "someone has so much work"},
        {"front": "take (something) with a pinch of salt", "back": "something is not reliable"},
        {"front": "right as rain", "back": "in perfect health"},
        {"front": "live and learn", "back": ""},
        {"front": "give someone a run for their money", "back": "challenge them at something they're good at"},
        {"front": "to butter someone up", "back": "compliment them usually to get something else from them"},
        {"front": "raring to go", "back": "eager to do a task"},
        {"front": "shake it off", "back": "forget some bad memory to stop it keep annoying you"},
        {"front": "riding a bike", "back": "skill that cannot forget"},
        {"front": "the salt of the earth", "back": "extreme good person"},
        {"front": "one man's trash is another man's treausre", "back": "people value different things"},
        {"front": "happy days", "back": "react to some happy situation"},
        {"front": "to kill two birds with one stone", "back": ""},
        {"front": "the best of both worlds", "back": "get benefits from two different situation"},
        {"front": "waste not want not", "back": "don't waste"},
        {"front": "every little helps", "back": ""},
        {"front": "understand the assignment", "back": ""},
        {"front": "digital detox", "back": "away from internet/digital world for a period of time"},
        {"front": "to jump the shark", "back": "someone do some ridiculous thing"},
        {"front": "first world problem", "back": "refer to problem that only happened in developed countries, usually meaning it's not really a problem"},
        {"front": "to hug it out", "back": "to finish the argument"},
        {"front": "you cannot rush perfection", "back": ""},
        {"front": "step your game up", "back": "tell someone to do better"},
        {"front": "to have bigger fish to fry", "back": "you have a bigger problem that needs more attention"},
        {"front": "comfort food", "back": "food that let you feel better"},
        {"front": "to jump on the bandwagon", "back": "start liking something many like"},
        {"front": "wear your heart on your sleeve", "back": "not good at hiding emotion"},
        {"front": "old school", "back": "old fashion"},
        {"front": "beat around the bush", "back": "avoid saying the thing needed to be said"},
        {"front": "sit tight", "back": "wait there"},
        {"front": "get wind of something", "back": "get some rumor of something"},
        {"front": "no smoke without fire", "back": "sign of something happening, it propably is going to happen"},
        {"front": "not the sharpest tool in the shed", "back": "someone is stupid"},
        {"front": "let the dust settle", "back": "let situation calm down before doing something"},
        {"front": "elephant in the room", "back": ""},
        {"front": "perfect storm", "back": "bad situation happened beacuse many tiny elements combied"},
        {"front": "not one's first rodeo", "back": "have past experience on something"},
        {"front": "to sign one's life away", "back": "funny way to tell someone to sign something"}
    ],
    "Smashing English (Restaurant)": [
        {"front": "Could I make a booking for <x> people at <time> on <date> please", "back": ""},
        {"front": "I made a booking earlier at <time>, my name is <xxx>", "back": ""},
        {"front": "do we order at the bar or is it table service?", "back": ""},
        {"front": "Could I have a high chair for children?", "back": ""},
        {"front": "Could I have the children menu?", "back": ""},
        {"front": "Could I have an allergen menu please?", "back": ""},
        {"front": "Yes I'm allergic to corn/nuts....", "back": ""},
        {"front": "Could I have the pizza? / I'll go for the pizza.", "back": ""},
        {"front": "Everything okay with your meal? Great, thanks", "back": ""},
        {"front": "Could we have the bill please?", "back": ""}
    ],
    "Smashing English (Home related)": [
        {"front": "Landing (top of the stairs)", "back": ""},
        {"front": "Master/Main bedroom/Master Suite (biggest bedroom)", "back": ""},
        {"front": "double bed -> Queen size bed -> King size bed", "back": ""},
        {"front": "bedside table", "back": ""},
        {"front": "chest of drawers", "back": ""},
        {"front": "rug (a little piece of carpet)", "back": ""},
        {"front": "washing up basket", "back": ""},
        {"front": "wardrobe", "back": ""},
        {"front": "Second bedroom", "back": ""},
        {"front": "Box room", "back": ""},
        {"front": "Rain head shower", "back": ""},
        {"front": "tap", "back": ""},
        {"front": "porch", "back": ""},
        {"front": "bannister (similar to handrail but in your house)", "back": ""},
        {"front": "living room/sitting room/lounge", "back": ""},
        {"front": "mantelpiece", "back": ""},
        {"front": "sideboard/ cabinet", "back": ""},
        {"front": "open plan kitchen", "back": ""},
        {"front": "extractor fan", "back": ""},
        {"front": "hob", "back": ""},
        {"front": "grill", "back": ""}
    ],
    "Smashing English (100+ Adjectives)": [
        {"front": "stoic", "back": "not showind emotion"},
        {"front": "tenacious", "back": "extremely determined"},
        {"front": "empathetic", "back": "aware of other feelings"},
        {"front": "resolute", "back": "know exact your goal/believe and going to change"},
        {"front": "prophetic", "back": "give people wisdom / predict future"},
        {"front": "noble", "back": "good / right / true"},
        {"front": "aspirational", "back": "go for big dream"},
        {"front": "introspective", "back": ""},
        {"front": "self-righteous", "back": "believe self doing something right"},
        {"front": "privileged", "back": ""},
        {"front": "Dapper", "back": "dress well"},
        {"front": "Affuent", "back": "lifestyle that show youre wealth"},
        {"front": "Vain", "back": "love yourself, find yourself attractive"},
        {"front": "dramatic", "back": ""},
        {"front": "clueless", "back": "doesn't know whats going on"},
        {"front": "shredded", "back": "got muscule"},
        {"front": "shallow", "back": "only care looks"},
        {"front": "simple-minded", "back": ""},
        {"front": "dense", "back": "stupid in a more aggressive way to say"},
        {"front": "Suave", "back": "quite charm"},
        {"front": "mischievous", "back": ""},
        {"front": "witty", "back": "able to make joke on different sitution"},
        {"front": "precocious", "back": "children act a lot older than they are, usually a bit annoying"},
        {"front": "streetwise", "back": "know about real life"},
        {"front": "rebellious", "back": ""},
        {"front": "impulsive", "back": "don't think through very well before doing something"},
        {"front": "energetic", "back": ""},
        {"front": "bratty", "back": ""},
        {"front": "infantile", "back": "acting like a baby"},
        {"front": "puerile", "back": "acting like a baby"},
        {"front": "exasperating", "back": "extremely annoying"},
        {"front": "desperate", "back": "will do anything to achieve something, nothing to lose"},
        {"front": "resourceful", "back": "able to use thing in surrounding as your advantage"},
        {"front": "determined", "back": "people who dun give up"},
        {"front": "strategic", "back": "good at planning what to do"},
        {"front": "scruffy", "back": "not looking smart"},
        {"front": "expressive", "back": "good at showing their emotion"},
        {"front": "desolate", "back": "got nothing to lose"},
        {"front": "decent", "back": "good people"},
        {"front": "vulnerable", "back": "weak"},
        {"front": "pessimistic", "back": "opposite to optimistic"},
        {"front": "calculating", "back": "always thinking to manipulate / take advantage of someone/something"},
        {"front": "ruthless", "back": "get something no matter what"},
        {"front": "disciplined", "back": "keep doing what is needed to do, dun get lazy"},
        {"front": "methodical", "back": "doing thing with a method"},
        {"front": "vengeful", "back": ""},
        {"front": "sophisticated", "back": ""},
        {"front": "multifaceted", "back": ""},
        {"front": "two-faced", "back": ""},
        {"front": "analytical", "back": ""},
        {"front": "eloquent", "back": "good at persuading people"},
        {"front": "self-serving", "back": ""},
        {"front": "cold", "back": ""},
        {"front": "Prim", "back": "elegant, always well behaved"},
        {"front": "snooty", "back": "look down on things you dun like"},
        {"front": "particular", "back": "know exactly what one's want"},
        {"front": "straight-laced", "back": "old fashioned"},
        {"front": "magical", "back": "amazing person"},
        {"front": "nurturing", "back": "help kid grow/ to be better"},
        {"front": "whimsical", "back": "light/ playful"},
        {"front": "authoritative", "back": ""},
        {"front": "self-assured", "back": "confidence in oneself; dun doubt oneself"},
        {"front": "musical", "back": ""},
        {"front": "no-nonsense", "back": "dun accept nonsense"},
        {"front": "complex", "back": ""},
        {"front": "intense", "back": "not playful, quite serious"},
        {"front": "enigmatic", "back": "hard to understand"},
        {"front": "tormented", "back": "feel awful about something one's done"},
        {"front": "compelling", "back": ""},
        {"front": "influential", "back": ""},
        {"front": "divisive", "back": ""},
        {"front": "haunted", "back": "always thinking horrible thing one's done"},
        {"front": "flawed", "back": ""},
        {"front": "fiesty", "back": "stand up for oneself more"},
        {"front": "conflicted", "back": "dun know what to do"},
        {"front": "spirited", "back": "lot of personality/opinion"},
        {"front": "romantic", "back": ""},
        {"front": "headstrong", "back": "strong in head, exactly what to want; clever;"},
        {"front": "iconic", "back": ""},
        {"front": "competent", "back": "able to do lot of thing"},
        {"front": "opinionated", "back": "lot of opinion"},
        {"front": "hopeless", "back": ""},
        {"front": "sheltered", "back": "doesn't know the world/people"},
        {"front": "confined", "back": "feel trap in a small space"},
        {"front": "indecisive", "back": ""},
        {"front": "naive", "back": "dun know things"},
        {"front": "preppy", "back": "academic style"},
        {"front": "idealistic", "back": ""},
        {"front": "academic", "back": ""},
        {"front": "well-meaning", "back": "intentions are good"},
        {"front": "ambitious", "back": "have a big goal"},
        {"front": "evolving", "back": "changing"},
        {"front": "unworldly", "back": "doesn't understand the real world"},
        {"front": "snobby", "back": ""},
        {"front": "resentful", "back": "keep negative emtion in oneself"},
        {"front": "deranged", "back": "really crazy"},
        {"front": "unpredictable", "back": ""},
        {"front": "merciless", "back": ""},
        {"front": "manic", "back": "insane"},
        {"front": "exuberant", "back": "personality/thinking big"},
        {"front": "theatrical", "back": ""},
        {"front": "wicked", "back": "evil"},
        {"front": "arrogant", "back": "think one self is better than others"},
        {"front": "repulsive", "back": "disgusting"},
        {"front": "emotional", "back": ""}
    ],
    "Smashing English (Common British Slangs A-Z 26words)": [
        {"front": "Allow it", "back": "leave something alone, dun worry about it"},
        {"front": "Bonkers", "back": "crazy"},
        {"front": "Cheeky", "back": "not polite in a funny way"},
        {"front": "Donkey's years", "back": "a very long time"},
        {"front": "effing and jeffing", "back": "polite way to say someone is very angry and swearing a lot"},
        {"front": "faff", "back": "a job require a lot of effort"},
        {"front": "gobby", "back": "someone is loud and wont stop talking"},
        {"front": "hammered", "back": "drunk"},
        {"front": "I'm not being funny", "back": "being serious"},
        {"front": "jammy", "back": "lucky"},
        {"front": "kip", "back": "nap"},
        {"front": "loo", "back": "toliet"},
        {"front": "melt", "back": "wimp, pathetic and a bit of a idiot"},
        {"front": "naff", "back": "not good, bad in quality"},
        {"front": "out out", "back": ""},
        {"front": "peak", "back": "rude or brutally honest"},
        {"front": "quid", "back": "pound as in money"},
        {"front": "rah", "back": "exclamtion"},
        {"front": "skint", "back": "Im broke"},
        {"front": "To-Do", "back": "party or a big event"},
        {"front": "Umpteen", "back": "number so big so we lost count"},
        {"front": "vino", "back": "wine"},
        {"front": "wee", "back": ""},
        {"front": "xtra", "back": ""},
        {"front": "you what?", "back": "what did you say in an angry way"},
        {"front": "zonked", "back": "very tired"}
    ],
    "Ari iTalki Class": [
        {"front": "I am", "back": "Yo soy"},
        {"front": "You are", "back": "Tu eres"},
        {"front": "He is", "back": "El es"},
        {"front": "She is", "back": "Ella es"},
        {"front": "You are (formal)", "back": "Usted es"},
        {"front": "We are", "back": "Nosotros somos"},
        {"front": "They are (M)", "back": "Ellos son"},
        {"front": "They are (F)", "back": "Ellas son"},
        {"front": "You guys", "back": "Ustedes son"},
        {"front": "nice (adj)", "back": "simpatico(s) / simpatica(s)"},
        {"front": "smart (adj)", "back": "inteligente(s)"},
        {"front": "funny (adj)", "back": "gracioso(s) / graciosa(s)"},
        {"front": "polite (adj)", "back": "educado(s) / educada(s)"},
        {"front": "rude (adj)", "back": "maleducado(s) / maleducada(s)"},
        {"front": "but", "back": "pero"},
        {"front": "tall (adj)", "back": "alto(s) / alta(s)"},
        {"front": "short (adj)", "back": "bajo(s) / baja(s)"},
        {"front": "old (adj)", "back": "viejo(s) / vieja(s)"},
        {"front": "young (adj)", "back": "joven(es)"},
        {"front": "brunette (adj)", "back": "morocho(s) / morocha(s)"},
        {"front": "blonde (adj)", "back": "rubio(s) / rubia(s)"},
        {"front": "man", "back": "hombre"},
        {"front": "woman", "back": "mujer"},
        {"front": "guy", "back": "muchacho"},
        {"front": "girl", "back": "muchacha"},
        {"front": "kid", "back": "niNo / niNa"},
        {"front": "the(F)", "back": "la / las"},
        {"front": "the(M)", "back": "el / los"},
        {"front": "Como es tu amigo", "back": "How is your friend(characteristically): El es alto"},
        {"front": "Como esta tu amigo", "back": "How is your friend(feeling): El esta muy bien"},
        {"front": "big (adj)", "back": "grande(s)"},
        {"front": "little (adj)", "back": "pequeNo(s) / pequeNa(s)"},
        {"front": "fast (adj)", "back": "rapido(s) / rapida(s)"},
        {"front": "slow (adj)", "back": "lento(s) / lenta(s)"},
        {"front": "cheap (adj)", "back": "barato(s) / barata(s)"},
        {"front": "expensive (adj)", "back": "caro(s) / cara(s)"},
        {"front": "tasty (adj)", "back": "delicioso(s) / deliciosa(s)"},
        {"front": "house", "back": "casa"},
        {"front": "car", "back": "coche / carro / auto"},
        {"front": "food", "back": "comida"},
        {"front": "clothes", "back": "ropa"},
        {"front": "water", "back": "el agua"},
        {"front": "my", "back": "mi / mis"},
        {"front": "your", "back": "tu / tus"},
        {"front": "his, her", "back": "su / sus"},
        {"front": "our", "back": "nuestro(s) / nuestra(s)"},
        {"front": "their", "back": "sus"},
        {"front": "the car's my dad", "back": "el coche de mi papa"},
        {"front": "ciudad", "back": "city"},
        {"front": "The food in my city is expensive", "back": "la comida en mi ciudad es cara"}
    ],
    "Hiragana": [
        {"front": "あ", "back": "a"},
        {"front": "い", "back": "i"},
        {"front": "う", "back": "u"},
        {"front": "え", "back": "e"},
        {"front": "お", "back": "o"},
        {"front": "か", "back": "ka"},
        {"front": "き", "back": "ki"},
        {"front": "く", "back": "ku"},
        {"front": "け", "back": "ke"},
        {"front": "こ", "back": "ko"},
        {"front": "さ", "back": "sa"},
        {"front": "し", "back": "shi"},
        {"front": "す", "back": "su"},
        {"front": "せ", "back": "se"},
        {"front": "そ", "back": "so"},
        {"front": "た", "back": "ta"},
        {"front": "ち", "back": "chi"},
        {"front": "つ", "back": "tsu"},
        {"front": "て", "back": "te"},
        {"front": "と", "back": "to"},
        {"front": "な", "back": "na"},
        {"front": "に", "back": "ni"},
        {"front": "ぬ", "back": "nu"},
        {"front": "ね", "back": "ne"},
        {"front": "の", "back": "no"},
        {"front": "ま", "back": "ma"},
        {"front": "み", "back": "mi"},
        {"front": "む", "back": "mu"},
        {"front": "め", "back": "me"},
        {"front": "も", "back": "mo"},
        {"front": "は", "back": "ha"},
        {"front": "ひ", "back": "hi"},
        {"front": "ふ", "back": "fu"},
        {"front": "へ", "back": "he"},
        {"front": "ほ", "back": "ho"},
        {"front": "ら", "back": "ra"},
        {"front": "り", "back": "ri"},
        {"front": "る", "back": "ru"},
        {"front": "れ", "back": "re"},
        {"front": "ろ", "back": "ro"},
        {"front": "や", "back": "ya"},
        {"front": "ゆ", "back": "yu"},
        {"front": "よ", "back": "yo"},
        {"front": "ん", "back": "n"},
        {"front": "が", "back": "ga"},
        {"front": "ぎ", "back": "gi"},
        {"front": "ぐ", "back": "gu"},
        {"front": "げ", "back": "ge"},
        {"front": "ご", "back": "go"},
        {"front": "ざ", "back": "za"},
        {"front": "じ", "back": "ji"},
        {"front": "ず", "back": "zu"},
        {"front": "ぜ", "back": "ze"},
        {"front": "ぞ", "back": "zo"},
        {"front": "ば", "back": "ba"},
        {"front": "び", "back": "bi"},
        {"front": "ぶ", "back": "bu"},
        {"front": "べ", "back": "be"},
        {"front": "ぼ", "back": "bo"},
        {"front": "ぱ", "back": "pa"},
        {"front": "ぴ", "back": "pi"},
        {"front": "ぷ", "back": "pu"},
        {"front": "ぺ", "back": "pe"},
        {"front": "ぽ", "back": "po"},
        {"front": "だ", "back": "da"},
        {"front": "ぢ", "back": "ji"},
        {"front": "づ", "back": "zu"},
        {"front": "で", "back": "de"},
        {"front": "ど", "back": "do"},
        {"front": "きゃ", "back": "kya"},
        {"front": "じゅ", "back": "kyu"},
        {"front": "じょ", "back": "kyo"},
        {"front": "ぎゃ", "back": "gya"},
        {"front": "ぎゅ", "back": "gyu"},
        {"front": "ぎょ", "back": "gyo"},
        {"front": "しゃ", "back": "sha"},
        {"front": "しゅ", "back": "shu"},
        {"front": "しょ", "back": "sho"},
        {"front": "じゃ", "back": "ja"},
        {"front": "じゅ", "back": "ju"},
        {"front": "じょ", "back": "jo"},
        {"front": "ちゃ", "back": "cha"},
        {"front": "ちゅ", "back": "chu"},
        {"front": "ちょ", "back": "cho"},
        {"front": "にゃ", "back": "nya"},
        {"front": "にゅ", "back": "nyu"},
        {"front": "にょ", "back": "nyo"},
        {"front": "ひゃ", "back": "hya"},
        {"front": "ひゅ", "back": "hyu"},
        {"front": "ひょ", "back": "hyo"},
        {"front": "びゃ", "back": "bya"},
        {"front": "びゅ", "back": "byu"},
        {"front": "びょ", "back": "byo"},
        {"front": "ぴゃ", "back": "pya"},
        {"front": "ぴゅ", "back": "pyu"},
        {"front": "ぴょ", "back": "pyo"},
        {"front": "みゃ", "back": "mya"},
        {"front": "みゅ", "back": "myu"},
        {"front": "みょ", "back": "myo"},
        {"front": "りゃ", "back": "rya"},
        {"front": "りゅ", "back": "ryu"},
        {"front": "りょ", "back": "ryo"}
    ],
    "Katakana": [
        {"front": "ア", "back": "a"},
        {"front": "イ", "back": "i"},
        {"front": "ウ", "back": "u"},
        {"front": "エ", "back": "e"},
        {"front": "オ", "back": "o"},
        {"front": "カ", "back": "ka"},
        {"front": "キ", "back": "ki"},
        {"front": "ク", "back": "ku"},
        {"front": "ケ", "back": "ke"},
        {"front": "コ", "back": "ko"},
        {"front": "サ", "back": "sa"},
        {"front": "シ", "back": "shi"},
        {"front": "ス", "back": "su"},
        {"front": "セ", "back": "se"},
        {"front": "ソ", "back": "so"},
        {"front": "タ", "back": "ta"},
        {"front": "チ", "back": "chi"},
        {"front": "ツ", "back": "tsu"},
        {"front": "テ", "back": "te"},
        {"front": "ト", "back": "to"},
        {"front": "ナ", "back": "na"},
        {"front": "ニ", "back": "ni"},
        {"front": "ヌ", "back": "nu"},
        {"front": "ネ", "back": "ne"},
        {"front": "ノ", "back": "no"},
        {"front": "マ", "back": "ma"},
        {"front": "ミ", "back": "mi"},
        {"front": "ム", "back": "mu"},
        {"front": "メ", "back": "me"},
        {"front": "モ", "back": "mo"},
        {"front": "ハ", "back": "ha"},
        {"front": "ヒ", "back": "hi"},
        {"front": "フ", "back": "fu"},
        {"front": "ヘ", "back": "he"},
        {"front": "ホ", "back": "ho"},
        {"front": "ラ", "back": "ra"},
        {"front": "リ", "back": "ri"},
        {"front": "ル", "back": "ru"},
        {"front": "レ", "back": "re"},
        {"front": "ロ", "back": "ro"},
        {"front": "ヤ", "back": "ya"},
        {"front": "ユ", "back": "yu"},
        {"front": "ヨ", "back": "yo"},
        {"front": "ン", "back": "n"},
        {"front": "ガ", "back": "ga"},
        {"front": "ギ", "back": "gi"},
        {"front": "グ", "back": "gu"},
        {"front": "ゲ", "back": "ge"},
        {"front": "ゴ", "back": "go"},
        {"front": "ザ", "back": "za"},
        {"front": "ジ", "back": "ji"},
        {"front": "ズ", "back": "zu"},
        {"front": "ゼ", "back": "ze"},
        {"front": "ゾ", "back": "zo"},
        {"front": "バ", "back": "ba"},
        {"front": "ビ", "back": "bi"},
        {"front": "ブ", "back": "bu"},
        {"front": "ベ", "back": "be"},
        {"front": "ボ", "back": "bo"},
        {"front": "パ", "back": "pa"},
        {"front": "ピ", "back": "pi"},
        {"front": "プ", "back": "pu"},
        {"front": "ペ", "back": "pe"},
        {"front": "ポ", "back": "po"},
        {"front": "ダ", "back": "da"},
        {"front": "ジ", "back": "ji"},
        {"front": "ズ", "back": "zu"},
        {"front": "デ", "back": "de"},
        {"front": "ド", "back": "do"},
        {"front": "キャ", "back": "kya"},
        {"front": "キュ", "back": "kyu"},
        {"front": "キョ", "back": "kyo"},
        {"front": "ギャ", "back": "gya"},
        {"front": "ギュ", "back": "gyu"},
        {"front": "ギョ", "back": "gyo"},
        {"front": "シャ", "back": "sha"},
        {"front": "シュ", "back": "shu"},
        {"front": "ショ", "back": "sho"},
        {"front": "ジャ", "back": "ja"},
        {"front": "ジュ", "back": "ju"},
        {"front": "ジョ", "back": "jo"},
        {"front": "チャ", "back": "cha"},
        {"front": "チュ", "back": "chu"},
        {"front": "ちょ", "back": "cho"},
        {"front": "ニャ", "back": "nya"},
        {"front": "ニュ", "back": "nyu"},
        {"front": "ニョ", "back": "nyo"},
        {"front": "ヒャ", "back": "hya"},
        {"front": "ヒュ", "back": "hyu"},
        {"front": "ヒョ", "back": "hyo"},
        {"front": "ビャ", "back": "bya"},
        {"front": "ビュ", "back": "byu"},
        {"front": "ビョ", "back": "byo"},
        {"front": "ピャ", "back": "pya"},
        {"front": "ピュ", "back": "pyu"},
        {"front": "ピョ", "back": "pyo"},
        {"front": "ミャ", "back": "mya"},
        {"front": "ミュ", "back": "myu"},
        {"front": "ミョ", "back": "myo"},
        {"front": "リャ", "back": "rya"},
        {"front": "リュ", "back": "ryu"},
        {"front": "リョ", "back": "ryo"}
    ],
    "Genki Book 1": [
        {"front": "おはよう", "back": "お早う　Good Morning"},
        {"front": "おはようございます", "back": "Good Morning(polite)"},
        {"front": "こんいちは", "back": "今日は　Good Afternoon"},
        {"front": "こんばんわ", "back": "今晩は　Good Evening"},
        {"front": "さようなら", "back": "Good-Bye"},
        {"front": "おやすみなさい", "back": "Good night"},
        {"front": "ありがとう", "back": "Thank you"},
        {"front": "ありがとうございます", "back": "Thank you(polite)"},
        {"front": "すみません", "back": "Execuse me"},
        {"front": "いいえ", "back": "No; Not at all"},
        {"front": "いってきます", "back": "I'll go and come back"},
        {"front": "いってらっしゃい", "back": "Please go and come back"},
        {"front": "ただいま", "back": "I'm home"},
        {"front": "おかえりなさい", "back": "お帰りなさい　Welcome home"},
        {"front": "いただきます", "back": "Thank you for the meal(Before eating)"},
        {"front": "ごちそうさまでした", "back": "Thank you for the meal(after eating)"},
        {"front": "はじめまして", "back": "初めまして　How do you do?"},
        {"front": "よろしくおねがいします", "back": "よろしくお願いします　Nice to meet you"},
        {"front": "あの", "back": "um..."},
        {"front": "いま", "back": "now"},
        {"front": "えいご", "back": "英語　English"},
        {"front": "ええ", "back": "yes"},
        {"front": "がくせい", "back": "学生　student"},
        {"front": "～ご", "back": "～語　language"},
        {"front": "にほんご", "back": "日本語　Japanese"},
        {"front": "こうこう", "back": "高校　high school"},
        {"front": "ごご", "back": "午後　P.M."},
        {"front": "ごぜん", "back": "午前　A.M."},
        {"front": "さい", "back": "_years old"},
        {"front": "さん", "back": "Mr/Ms..."},
        {"front": "じ", "back": "o'clock"},
        {"front": "じン", "back": "人　_people"},
        {"front": "せんこう", "back": "専攻　major"},
        {"front": "せんせい", "back": "先生　teacher or professor"},
        {"front": "そうです", "back": "that's right"},
        {"front": "そうですか", "back": "I see"},
        {"front": "だいがく", "back": "大学　college"},
        {"front": "でんわ", "back": "電話　telephone"},
        {"front": "ともだち", "back": "友達　friend"},
        {"front": "なまえ", "back": "名前　name"},
        {"front": "なん　なに", "back": "what"},
        {"front": "にほん", "back": "日本　Japan"},
        {"front": "ねんせい", "back": "年生　_year student"},
        {"front": "はい", "back": "yes"},
        {"front": "はん", "back": "半　half"},
        {"front": "ばんごう", "back": "番号　number"},
        {"front": "りゅうがくせい", "back": "留学生　international student"},
        {"front": "わたし", "back": "私　I"},
        {"front": "アメリカ", "back": "亜米利加　USA"},
        {"front": "イギリス", "back": "Britain"},
        {"front": "オオストラリア", "back": "Australia"},
        {"front": "かんこく", "back": "韓国　Korea"},
        {"front": "スウエエデン", "back": "Sweden"},
        {"front": "ちゅうごく", "back": "中国　China"},
        {"front": "かがく", "back": "科学　science"},
        {"front": "アジアけんきゅう", "back": "Asian studies"},
        {"front": "けいざい", "back": "経済　economics"},
        {"front": "こくさいかんけい", "back": "国際関係　international relations"},
        {"front": "コンピューター", "back": "computer"},
        {"front": "じんるいかんけい", "back": "人類学　anthropology"},
        {"front": "せいじ", "back": "政治　politics"},
        {"front": "ビジネス", "back": "business"},
        {"front": "ぶんがく", "back": "文学　literature"},
        {"front": "れきし", "back": "歴史　history"},
        {"front": "しごと", "back": "仕事　job; work; occupations"},
        {"front": "いしゃ", "back": "医者　doctor"},
        {"front": "かいしゃいん", "back": "会社員　clerk"},
        {"front": "こうこうせい", "back": "高校生　high school student"},
        {"front": "しゅふ", "back": "主婦　housewife"},
        {"front": "だいがくいんせい", "back": "大学院生　graduate student"},
        {"front": "だいがくせい", "back": "大学生　college student"},
        {"front": "べんごし", "back": "弁護士　lawyer"},
        {"front": "おかあさん", "back": "お母さん　mother"},
        {"front": "おとうさん", "back": "お父さん　father"},
        {"front": "おねえさん", "back": "お姉さん　older sister"},
        {"front": "おにいさん", "back": "お兄さん　older brother"},
        {"front": "いもうと", "back": "妹　younger sister"},
        {"front": "おとうと", "back": "弟　younger brother"}
    ]
}